question_data = [

    {"type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
     "question": "In the 1988 film &quot;Akira&quot;, Tetsuo ends up destroying Tokyo.",
     "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Television",
     "question": "In &quot;Doctor Who&quot;, the Doctor gets his TARDIS by stealing it.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Musicals &amp; Theatres",
     "question": "In the play Oedipus Rex, Oedipus kills his father due to jealousy in loving his mother.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
     "question": "Stevie Wonder&#039;s real name is Stevland Hardaway Morris.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Science: Mathematics",
     "question": "A scalene triangle has two sides of equal length.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
     "question": "In the &quot;Melancholy of Haruhi Suzumiya&quot; series, the narrator goes by the nickname Kyon.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Mythology",
     "question": "A wyvern is the same as a dragon.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "History",
     "question": "Former United States Presidents John Adams and Thomas Jefferson died within hours of each other.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
     "question": "Eurobeat is primarily an Italian genre of music.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
     "question": "The anime &quot;Lucky Star&quot; follows the story of one girl who is unaware she is God.",
     "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}
]
